Guide to the Ernest J. Sternglass papers, [ca. 1952-2008]
Sternglass, Ernest J. papers
- Alphabetical File List
  - Nevada. Percent Life Birth Weight. Infant Mortality. Also Live Births Rise, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Nevada Sheep Trial, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Needleman, H.L., 1991-1996 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - New Mexico Breast Cancer Maps (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - New Orleans Breast Cancer and Environment (7/21/1995) (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - "New School" - Course Offered 1991 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - The New York Academy of Sciences. Experiment Summary Draft, 1984-1986 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - New York City Council - 1986 - Letter to Cuomo Urging Shut-Down of Indian Point (June 2, 1986 - Ruth Messinger) (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - New York City Immunodeficiency. Indian Point (4/28/1992), 1993 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - New York City, 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - New York Dumpsite Selection, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - New York Nuclear Waste Site, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - New York Infant Death Statistics, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Nine Mile Point, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - North Carolina Cancer Plots, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Nuclear Power Battle, 1982-1986 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission Radiation Studies, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Underground Nuclear Explosions, 1981-1986 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Nuclear Age Peace Foundation, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Radioactive Wastes to Atmosphere, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Nuclear Monitor, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Nuclear Test-Chinese Fallout, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Nuclear Proliferation, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Low Level Radiation-Gary Null, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Nussbaum, Rudi, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Number Theory-Gauss, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Nuclear Reactors-Safety, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Nuclear Weapons Plant, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Obesity, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Osteoporosis, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Fundamental Physics-Olympia, Greece, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Oyster Creek Nuclear Watch, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Ozone Hole, 1958-1996 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Ozone Layer Decline, 1980-1992 (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Ozone-Air Pollution, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Pauling, Linus, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Vital Statistics, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - PDA (Public Data Access)- Radioactive Emissions Data, 1965-1982 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - PDA - Mississippi River Study, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - PDA Proposals for State Studies, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - PDA Reports, 1976-1986 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - PDA Reports, 1978-1989 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Peach Bottom Nuclear Plant, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Perry Island, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Personal Health, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Pesticides, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Philadelphia Department of Public Health, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Pilgrim Nuclear Power Plant, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Pilgrim Nuclear Plant History (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Pilgrim Report, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Pisello, Daniel, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - PPituitary Gland, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Portsmouth Workshop on Radiation, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Plutonium Disposition, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Pottsville Hospital - Lynn Stiltner, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Poulin vs. Fleming, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Prairie Island Coalition, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Professionals Network for Social Responsibility, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Prostrate Cancer, 1985-1994 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Punnett Case - Law Suit (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Radiation Round Table, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Radiation Effects, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Radiation Experiments, 1974-1994 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Radioactive Waste Discharges, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Radioactive Victim's Conference, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Radon in Homes, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Rainfall Data, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Ratner, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Reichelt, Gunther, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Rhode Island Vital Statistics Report, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Rickover, Hyman-Three Mile Island (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Rockefeller University Testimony, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Federation of American Scientists Report, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Rocky Flats Problems, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Rochester N.Y.- Linda Garman, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Rongelap Island, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Rosenberg, Howard, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Sakharov, A, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Scholastic Aptitude Test and IQ, 1976-2000 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Sashin, Don - Electronic Mammography, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Diagnostic Imaging, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - SANE Newsletter, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - SARS Virus in China, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - SASE Talk, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Scheer, Jens, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Secret Radiation Experiments, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Shanon, Sara - Radiation Monitoring, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Sherman, Janette, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Shuttle Disaster, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Siegel, Edward, 1995-1998 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Shock Therapy, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Sierra Club Paper on Low Level Radiation, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Stewart, Alice - Low Level Radiation, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Solon, Leonard, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - South West College of Naturopathic Medicine, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Star Wars, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Stewart, Alice, 1978-2001 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Suicide Rates, 1980-1989 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Y, Ce, Sr 90 Data, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Sr 90, 1977-1982 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Star Wars, 1986-1988 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Star Wars, 1985-2000 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Sun Day Campaign, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Swiss Mortality Rise, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Teller, Edward, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Test Ban, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Thornburgh, Dick-Three Mile Island Crisis, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Three Mile Island, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Thyroid Cancer, 1988-1992 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Tokuhata, George- Study of Mortality Data for Pennsylvania, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Transnational Family Research, 1984-1986 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Toronto Vigier Symposium, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Tritium in Tucson, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Triga - Maryland, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Tritium Effects, 1968-1984 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Uranium Mine and Mill Tailings, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - United Nations Nuclear Disarmament Conference, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - U.S. Infant Mortality Rate, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Upton Article-Low Level Radiation, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - USSR-Infant Mortality, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Utah Cancer Decision, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Vicari vs GPU, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Videos-Environmental, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Vigier Notes, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Vitamins, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Videos-Health Hazards, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Wald, George-Letter on Radioactive Fallout, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Wales-Leukemia and Cancer, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Wasserman, Harvey, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Washington D.C. Area Reactor, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Water Pollution, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Westinghouse Demise, 1994-1998 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - West Valley Contamination, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Wheeler, John, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - WIPP Project (Waste Isolation Pilot Plant), 1989 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - WHYL Nuclear Plant - Heidelberg, Germany, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Whyte, Robin, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - YUCCA Mountain, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - EJS Papers and Personal Records, 1961-1991 (Box 25)
  - EJS Papers and Personal Records, 1941-1999 (Box 26)
  - EJS Study 2 - 1995 Papers (Box 27)
  - Cosmology Papers, 1990-1998 (Box 28)
  - Elementary Particles - Cosmology 1, 1966-2000 (Box 29)
  - Elementary Particles - Cosmology 2, 1985-1998 (Box 30)
  - Cosmology 3, 1989-1998 (Box 31)
  - Cosmology 4, Philosophy of Science 1, 1980's (Box 32)
  - Philosophy of Science 2, 1966-1998 (Box 33)
  - Low Level Radiation 1, 1950-2003 (Box 34)
  - Low Level Radiation 2, 1957-1995 (Box 35)
  - Correspondence, 1996-2007 (Box 36)
  - Correspondence, 1996-2001 (Box 37)
  - Correspondence, 1949-1981 (Box 38)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1985 (Box 39)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1981 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1985 (Box 41)
  - Correspondence, 1963-1978 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous Papers, 1979-1983 (Box 43)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous Papers, 1966-1979 (Box 44)
  - Correspondence and Clippings; Nuclear Battle (1); Breast Cancer File, 1995-1997 (Box 45)
  - Correspondence and Clippings (2), 1980-1990 (Box 46)
  - 1961 Correspondence and Clippings (1), 1943-1972 (Box 47)
  - Correspondence and Clippings, TMI, 1976-1988 (Box 48)
  - Files, Correspondence, 1988-1995 (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous Files, 1976-1995 (Box 50)
  - Westinghouse (1), 1963-1971 (Box 51)
  - Westinghouse (2), Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1955-1991 (Box 52)
  - PDA, 1970-1986 (Box 53)
  - PDA, PDA Files TMI, 1979-1987 (Box 54)
  - PDA, 1963-1985 (Box 55)
  - PDA Files TMI, 1978-1983 (Box 56)
  - PDA, 1962-1984 (Box 57)
  - Radiation, 1980-1990 (Box 58)
  - Radiation, 1980-1990 (Box 59)
  - Correspondence, Radiation Data, 1980-1990 (Box 60)
  - Correspondence, Radiation Data, 1980-1990 (Box 61)
  - Nuclear Fallout, 1980-1990 (Box 62)
  - Milk Market, 1970-1990 (Box 63)
  - Milk Market, 1950-1980 (Box 64)
  - Card Files (Box 65)
  - Card Files (Box 66)
  - Card Files, Desk Files (Box 67)
  - Clippings and Files (Box 68)
  - Files (Box 69)
  - Files (Box 70)
  - Clippings, 1970's (Box 71)
  - Correspondence and Clippings, 1970's (Box 72)
  - Correspondence and Clippings, 1980's (Box 73)
  - Clippings, 1990's (Box 74)
  - Clippings: Aids, Chernobyl, 1985-1993 (Box 75)
  - Clippings and Correspondence, 1962-1972 (Box 76)
  - SAT Scores and Fallout, Three Mile Island Study, 1970's-1990's (Box 77)
  - Manuals and Clippings, 1990's (Box 78)
  - Drawings (Box 79)
  - Patent Boods (Box 80)
  - Videos (Box 81)
  - Videos (Box 82)
  - Photos (Box 83)
  - Environmental Radiation Reports, 1974-1987 (Box 83)
  - Notebook, September 18, 1946 - September 10, 1949 (Box 84)
  - Summary Notebook, May 15, 1949 - May 17, 1977 (Box 84)
  - Notebook. Secondary Emission [Record, Hard Cover], July 11, 1950 - February 23, 1951 (Box 84)
  - Notebook. SE Theory [Record, Hard Cover], March 30, 1951 - November 7, 1954 (Box 84)
  - Notebook [Spiral. Cornell], July 7, 1951 - November 7, 1951 (Box 84)
  - Notebook [Spiral. Cornell], November 11, 1951 - August 3, 1953 (Box 84)
  - Notebook [Record, Hard Cover], April 8, 1952 - June 6, 1953 (Box 84)
  - Westinghouse Notebook 1, August 15, 1952 - October 21, 1953 (Box 84)
  - Westinghouse Notebook 2, October 22, 1953 - March 19, 1954 (Box 84)
  - Westinghouse Notebook 2A, February 22, 1954 - September 25, 1954 (Box 84)
  - Westinghouse Notebook 3, March 22, 1954 - December 7, 1954 (Box 84)
  - Westinghouse Notebook 4, December 7, 1954 - February 10, 1955 (Box 84)
  - Westinghouse Notebook 5, February 10, 1955 - May 16, 1955 (Box 84)
  - Westinghouse Notebook 6, May 17, 1955 - July 4, 1955 (Box 84)
  - Westinghouse Notebook 7, July 8, 1955 - September 21, 1955 (Box 84)
  - Westinghouse Notebook 8, October 10, 1955 - January 12, 1956 (Box 84)
  - Westinghouse Notebook 9, February 8, 1956 - May 3, 1956 (Box 84)
  - Westinghouse Notebook 9A, February 8, 1956 - March 1, 1956 (Box 84)
  - Westinghouse Notebook 10, February 14, 1956 - October 11, 1956 (Box 84)
  - Westinghouse Notebook 11, October 15, 1956 - March 21, 1957 (Box 84)
  - Westinghouse Notebook 12, March 26, 1957 - September 23, 1957 (Box 84)
  - Notebook 1 [Spiral], February 10, 1958 - June 6, 1958 (Box 84)
  - Notebook 2 [Spiral], June 6, 1958 - June 27, 1958 (Box 84)
  - Notebook 3 [Spiral], July 3, 1958 - July 29, 1958 (Box 84)
  - Notebook 4 [Spiral], August 2, 1958 - August 13, 1958 (Box 84)
  - Notebook 5 [Spiral], August 14, 1958 - August 27, 1958 (Box 84)
  - Notebook 6 [Spiral], August 27, 1958 - September 28, 1958 (Box 84)
  - Notebook 7 [Spiral], September 29, 1958 - October 9, 1958 (Box 84)
  - Notebook 8 [Spiral], October 9, 1958 - October 17, 1958 (Box 84)
  - Notebook 9 [Spiral], October 17, 1958 - October 23, 1958 (Box 84)
  - Notebook 10 [Spiral], October 24, 1958 - November 4, 1958 (Box 84)
  - Notebook 11 (Last) [Spiral], November 5, 1958 - February 5, 1959 (Box 84)
  - Westinghouse Notebook, December 15, 1958 - January 12, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Westinghouse Notebook, January 12, 1959 - August 25, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 1 [Spiral], February 5, 1959 - March 6, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 2 [Spiral], March 6, 1959 - March 25, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 3 [Spiral], April 12, 1959 - April 21, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 4 [Spiral], April 21, 1959 - May 3, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 5 [Spiral], May 6, 1959 - May 25, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 6 [Spiral], May 25, 1959 - June 3, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 7 [Spiral], June 3, 1959 - June 14, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 8 [Spiral], June 14, 1959 - June 18, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 9 [Spiral], June 19, 1959 - July 19, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 10 [Spiral], July 19, 1959 - August 3, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 11 [Spiral], August 3, 1959 - August 11, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 12 [Spiral], August 12, 1959 - August 19, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 13 [Spiral], August 19, 1959 - August 29, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Westinghouse Notebook, August 26, 1959 - November 23, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 14 [Spiral], August 29, 1959 - September 3, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 15 [Spiral], September 3, 1959 - September 29, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 16 [Spiral], September 29, 1959 - December 11, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 1 [Spiral], October 28, 1959 - March 28, 1960 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 17 [Spiral], December 11, 1959 - December 21, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Westinghouse Notebook, December 15, 1959 - April 6, 1960 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 18 [Spiral], December 21, 1959 - December 30, 1959 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 19 [Spiral], December 30, 1959 - January 17, 1960 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 1, January 26, 1960 - August 3, 1960 (Box 85)
  - Westinghouse Notebook, April 6, 1960 - August 12, 1960 (Box 85)
  - Project Binder, July 1960 - January 9, 1961 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 2, August 3, 1960 - September 12, 1960 (Box 85)
  - Westinghouse Notebook, August 15, 1960 - October 30, 1960 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 3, September 12, 1960 - October 7, 1960 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 4, October 7, 1960 - November 12, 1960 (Box 85)
  - Westinghouse Notebook, November 3, 1960 - February 21, 1961 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 5, November 12, 1960 - January 2, 1961 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 6, January 3, 1960 - January 28, 1961 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 7, January 29, 1961 - April 2, 1961 (Box 85)
  - Westinghouse Notebook, February 23, 1961 - August 5, 1961 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 8, April 2, 1961 - June 30, 1961 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 9, June 30, 1961 - September 15, 1961 (Box 85)
  - Westinghouse Notebook, August 21, 1961 - October 30, 1961 (Box 85)
  - Notebook 10, September 15, 1961 - November 9, 1961 (Box 85)
  - Westinghouse Notebook, October 30, 1961 - February 16, 1962 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 11, November 9, 1961 - December 19, 1961 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 12, December 19, 1961 - April 3, 1962 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 13, April 3, 1962 - May 17, 1962 (Box 86)
  - Westinghouse Notebook, April 16, 1962 - July 18, 1963 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 14, May 17, 1962 - June 1, 1962 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 15, June 1, 1962 - June 17, 1962 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 16, June 17, 1962 - July 20, 1962 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 17, July 20, 1962 - November 15, 1962 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 18, November 15, 1962 - February 26, 1963 (Box 86)
  - Notebook [Space Science Study], February 5, 1963 - June 28, 1964 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 19, February 26, 1963 - October 5, 1963 (Box 86)
  - Westinghouse Notebook, September 4, 1963 - November 25, 1963 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 20, October 5, 1963 - November 6, 1963 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 21, November 6, 1963 - December 6, 1963 (Box 86)
  - Westinghouse Notebook, December 5, 1963 - November 19, 1964 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 22, December 6, 1963 - December 27, 1963 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 23, December 27, 1963 - January 11, 1964 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 24, January 11, 1964 - March 5, 1964 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 25, March 5, 1964 - July 17, 1964 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 26, July 17, 1964 - December 27, 1964 (Box 86)
  - Westinghouse Notebook, November 24, 1964 - February 15, 1965 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 27, December 27, 1964 - February 7, 1965 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 28, February 7, 1965 - September 21, 1965 (Box 86)
  - Westinghouse Notebook, February 15, 1965 - September 4, 1965 (Box 86)
  - Notebook [Space Science 2], July 15, 1965 - January 8, 1966 (Box 86)
  - Westinghouse Record Book, September 7, 1965 - November 2, 1967 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 29, September 21, 1965 - September 19, 1966 (Box 86)
  - Notebook [Space Science 3], February 8, 1966 - March 14, 1966 (Box 86)
  - Notebook 1 [Radiological Physics and Radiation Health], May 26, 1966 - October 10, 1966 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 30, September 19, 1966 - October 8, 1966 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 31, October 8, 1966 - October 23, 1966 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 2 [Radiological Physics and Radiation Health], October 10, 1966 - August 6, 1967 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 32, October 23, 1966 - November 4, 1966 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 33, November 4, 1966 - November 30, 1966 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 35, February 19, 1967 - August 10, 1967 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 3A [Radiological Physics - Camera Systems. Instrumentation], August 6, 1967 - April 19, 1968 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 3B [Radiological Physics and Radiation Effects], June 23, 1967 - November 12, 1967 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 36 [Elementary Particles], August 10, 1967 - June 1, 1968 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 4B [Radiological Physics and Radiation Effects. Low Level Radiation Effects], November 12, 1967 - March 10, 1968 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 5B [Radiological Physics and Radiation Effects. Low Level Radiation Effects], March 10, 1968 - September 29, 1968 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 9 A+B [Radiological Instruments and Low Level Radiation Effects], July 29, 1968 - January 21, 1969 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 6B [Radiological Physics and Radiation Effects. Low Level Radiation Effects], September 29, 1968 - October 23, 1968 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 7B [Radiological Physics and Radiation Effects. Low Level Radiation Effects], October 23, 1968 - November 30, 1968 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 8B [Radiological Physics and Radiation Effects. Low Level Radiation Effects], November 30, 1968 - December 29, 1968 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 10 [Radiation - Low Dose], January 31, 1969 - April 30, 1969 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 11 [Radiation - Low Dose], April 30, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 37A [Elementary Particles], June 4, 1969 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 12 [NASA - NIH - Radiation Effects], June 10, 1969 - October 31, 1969 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 13 [NASA - NIH - Radiation Effects], October 31, 1969 - January 30, 1970 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 14 [NASA - NIH - Radiation Effects], January 30, 1970 - July 20, 1970 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 15, July 20, 1970 - October 13, 1970 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 16, October 13, 1970 - December 4, 1970 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 17, December 4, 1970 - February 19, 1971 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 18, February 25, 1971 - April 4, 1971 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 19, April 13, 1971 - June 3, 1971 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 20, June 3, 1971 - September 30, 1971 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 21, September 30, 1971 - November 21, 1971 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 22, November 11, 1971 - January 25, 1972 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 23, January 25, 1972 - February 18, 1972 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 24, February 18, 1972 - March 31, 1972 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 25, March 31, 1972 - June 18, 1972 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 26, June 19, 1972 - August 28, 1972 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 27, August 28, 1972 - September 14, 1972 (Box 87)
  - Notebook 28, September 14, 1972 - October 8, 1972 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 29, October 8, 1972 - January 11, 1973 (Box 88)
  - Notebook [Spiral. Elementary Particles], October 15, 1972 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 30, January 11, 1973 - February 23, 1973 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 31, February 23, 1973 - March 17, 1973 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 32, March 17, 1973 - April 15, 1973 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 33, April 15, 1973 - June 23, 1973 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 34, June 23, 1973 - September 1, 1973 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 35, September 1, 1973 - October 21, 1973 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 36, October 21, 1973 - December 8, 1973 (Box 88)
  - Notebook [Shippingport Study], November 2, 1973 - February 15, 1974 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 37, December 8, 1973 - February 24, 1974 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 38, February 24, 1974 - April 1, 1974 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 39, April 1, 1974 - April 28, 1974 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 40, April 28, 1974 - May 18, 1974 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 41, May 18, 1974 - July 10, 1974 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 42, July 10, 1974 - August 30, 1974 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 43, August 30, 1974 - November 14, 1974 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 44, November 14, 1974 - November 26, 1974 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 45, November 26, 1974 - December 12, 1974 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 46, December 12, 1974 - December 22, 1974 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 47, December 22, 1974 - December 31, 1974 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 48, December 31, 1974 - January 6, 1975 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 49, January 6, 1975 - January 13, 1975 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 50, January 13, 1975 - January 19, 1975 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 51, January 19, 1975 - February 11, 1975 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 52, February 11, 1975 - March 7, 1975 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 53, March 7, 1975 - April 3, 1975 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 54, April 3, 1975 - May 5, 1975 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 55, May 5, 1975 - May 20, 1975 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 56, May 20, 1975 - June 6, 1975 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 57, June 6, 1975 - June 18, 1975 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 58, June 18, 1975 - June 30, 1975 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 59, June 30, 1975 - July 10, 1975 (Box 88)
  - Notebook 60, July 14, 1975 - July 24, 1975 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 61, July 24, 1975 - August 3, 1975 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 62, August 3, 1975 - September 8, 1975 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 63, September 8, 1975 - October 28, 1975 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 64, October 28, 1975 - January 3, 1976 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 65, January 3, 1976 - February 9, 1976 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 66, February 9, 1976 - February 26, 1976 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 67, February 26, 1976 - April 1, 1976 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 68, April 1, 1976 - April 17, 1976 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 69, April 17, 1976 - June 8, 1976 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 70, June 8, 1976 - July 13, 1976 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 71, July 13, 1976 - August 27, 1976 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 72, August 27, 1976 - September 24, 1976 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 73, September 24, 1976 - November 8, 1976 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 74, November 9, 1976 - March 23, 1977 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 75, March 23, 1977 - May 15, 1977 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 76, May 24, 1977 - June 13, 1977 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 77, June 13, 1977 - June 21, 1977 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 78, June 21, 1977 - July 11, 1977 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 79, July 12, 1977 - August 18, 1977 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 80, August 18, 1977 - September 6, 1977 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 81, September 6, 1977 - October 13, 1977 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 82, October 10, 1977 - November 12, 1977 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 83, November 12, 1977 - December 23, 1977 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 84, December 23, 1977 - january 10, 1978 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 85, January 10, 1978 - February 10, 1978 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 86, February 10, 1978 - March 12, 1978 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 87, March 12, 1978 - April 5, 1978 (Box 89)